thenewcircle.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy - NewCircle

### Effective: 02/19/2007

## Privacy Notice Table Of Contents

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * Special Notification for California Residents
  * How To Contact Us

## Our Commitment To Privacy

This site is owned and operated by NewCircle Inc. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At NewCircle, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the NewCircle.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. Personal information collected at these pages might include:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Organization name
  * Credit/Debit Card Information

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you register someone else for a course, or someone else, other then you, is paying for it, you will need to submit the their information. In this circumstance, personal information collected might include:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Organization name
  * Credit/Debit Card Information

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

The moment we successfully collect the payment your Credit Card information is purged from our system.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## Special Notification for California Residents

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our clients who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. To obtain such information, please contact us

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us
